[{"answer": "What I went through was real.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Plus, do you believe him?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, what you have to understand, after these horrific shootings that we go through, what the NRA does is already start to put out all the negative stuff, and then the members, to be very honest with you, start getting nervous about it.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What do you do to change their minds and therefore the chances of success of this attempt to change the law?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I have to tell you, and Representative McCarthy, thank you so much for your leadership.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How many more types do people need?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "I will tell you, if you talk to professionals, hunters and certainly sportsmen, they'll tell you that's probably not the kind of gun to use.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How do you respond to that particular argument, which is they believe under their Second Amendment right, they should be allowed an AR-15?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Yes, I believe in the American public.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Let me -- let me ask just very, very quickly, Michael Nutter, do you believe that you can win this argument and get an assault weapons ban reinstated?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "We have no idea.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you think that that could have played any part in causing him to suddenly go off like this?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "This is a semirural area outside of Albuquerque.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Did you have any information about that?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I can't get you a number, but I'll be glad -- I'll be glad to try to find a number.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "How many -- how many people of the three million who own AR-15s, military-style assault rifles in this country have ever used them to defend themselves?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "First of all, the civilian AR-15 is not an automatic weapon.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "I haven't heard of any, so the answer comes back at you, why does anybody need, in civilian life, a weapon that belongs in a military battlefield, as General Stanley McChrystal and General Colin Powell both said?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Because they were felt to be too dangerous.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Why are automatic weapons banned in America?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Because of high-volume of fire, which you don't get from a semiautomatic weapon.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Why are they too dangerous?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you know how many bullets the shooter at Aurora, James Holmes, fired per minute with his AR-15?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, by my criteria, and this goes back to the question of what you respect, Piers.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How many more bullets do you need to fire, Mr. Speaker, before that qualifies as a dangerous killing machine by your criteria?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "This is lovely propaganda.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "What else do you call them?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I would simply say to you that millions of people by your own definition own an AR-15.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What else do you call it?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "No, like this.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Do you know how many different types of guns she has permitted to remain in legal circulation in America under any proposal?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Why -- why would she permit twice as many.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "So this is what this year the government is willing to permit?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Wait a second.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "My position --", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Where are you on the pistols that killed most of the people in Chicago, Piers?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "It's OK if we kill them individually?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Let my position very, very clear.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Are you saying three, four, five, and that's OK?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Many of the other proposals --", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "So why don't you share your real view?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Let me -- let me explain what I would do.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Wouldn't you ban pistols if you could?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I think the founding fathers would have found this entire debate strange because they actually believed in individual freedom and they were very suspicious of big government, and they would find the idea that you're going to permit, to use the word you kept using.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "The semiautomatics that can fire 100 bullets in a minute are not dangerous and they should be lawful?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I think 50-caliber machine guns would be bizarre.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "But you do agree with not permitting Americans to have automatic weapons?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "To -- no, but now you're back to a different question.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Would that young man -- would that young man -- would that young men, have slaughtered five of his family if he hadn't had access to the firearms in the house?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "But, Newt, my final point is he clearly didn't protect them.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "You want to put -- so you're saying you want the state to step in?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I like your answer.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "It's a tragedy, we don't know all of the answers, but, you know, this is a situation where we want less Americans to be killed by guns, right?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Here is the thing, Piers, is the fact this is the most popular rifle in the United States.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Why do you need these mass killing machines?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "That's not the issue at hand right now, because they are banned.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Do you ladies agree with automatic weapons being banned?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Basically, that is something that I don't really --", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Do you believe automatic weapons should be banned, as they are?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Right now, yes.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Do you agree with the government's decision, which is an on-going law, to ban automatic weapons?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Both know that the basic difference is you pull the trigger and it shoots, as opposed to the automatic.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Can you explain that to me?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "For example, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Do you know one?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I believe -- I believe they should.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you believe that women should be allowed on the front line in combat in the military?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "To answer the first question, yes.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Am I basically not wise enough to America to understand why it's apparently not an infringement on the Second Amendment to ban automatic weapons, but it is to ban an AR-15 that can fire 100 bullets in a minute?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "It's not just you.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "It's not just me?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "There are some good organizations.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Where is that body having the same kind of political and financial muscle?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "There's never enough.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "When you see 2,200 guns can remain even with the proposal she's got, this apparently isn't dinged deemed enough to defend yourselves?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I thought she faired brilliantly.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Quick question on Hillary Clinton, how do you think she fared after the Benghazi hearings?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "No, because I don't feel like one.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Do you sit easily with the mantle of legend?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Here is the question I never thought I would ask John Elway, have you ever had a fake girlfriend?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Do you buy it all, from what you've seen?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "No, no, I'm not.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "So the question I guess for you now, since you are in this great high-powered position with the broncos, are you actively encouraging the Broncos now to have fake girlfriends in the hopes it boosts their play?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "He's a good player, a good football player.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "How good of a player is he?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "You know, I'm still kind of waiting to hear both sides of it.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "But as somebody who has grown up in American culture and presumably around guns, when you were a youngster, what is your view of the debate as it stands?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "No, that's one area.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "As someone who hunts, shoots, so on, for sport, do you see any need for a civilian to have one of these military style rifles that can pump out 100 bullets a minute?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "But do you see why anybody would need one as a civilian?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I don't know if you can define them as mistakes.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "What mistakes did they make, the Republicans, do you think?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "I can't bet, so my money isn't going anywhere.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Where is your money going?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Two good football teams.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Ravens and 49ers, who is going to take it?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "It's Dove Men Plus Care.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Tell me briefly about that?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Are you comfortable in your own skin, John?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "That takes a while.", "docId": "130124pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "How have you come to terms with not being able to be out there?", "qSentId": 701}]